This morning, Victor asked if I wanted to be a rabbit on his birthday paintball.
So now we drive!
My name is Mauri Hermundsson.
Since I became Youtuber I have started getting lots of requests in my inbox.
But I always say no because I'm a coward.
Now, however, there will be a change in that.
This week I will open my inbox every day and accept the first thing that shows up.
What strange places will it lead me to?
What unexpected people will I meet?
And how far will I be prepared to go?
- Do you want to take Elin Olander to your wife?
This section is also in collaboration with Wolt.
But now we are running.
- Monday we have cleared.
Now we will accept something new.
And the first thing that appeared now is that a woman named Pirjo wants to show me Finland.
You receive such mail.
That is why we do this section.
I get so heavenly random mail.
She did not write her number, but I will look for it.
- What are you looking for then?
- Just old men.
- Just old men?
- Yes, I think you might find someone.
I might find someone captain.
- You are craving the captain?
- You just never know, these nice hats and stuff.
Yes, and a little stomach and like this.
- Is it sexy?
- The old man should have some stomach.
- Not under 200 boilers?
300 kilos?
- No.
Where does the limit go?
- It's two and half.
- 250 kilos?
- But if he's big!
- You should suffocate when you are under him.
- or over.
- You should suffocate when you lie above him.
Then you are big.
- Who is the longest of us?
- I.
I have much more strength.
- Are you stronger?
- I can lift you.
- It's easier for me to lift you.
- Try
So!
So, don't!
Me too, me too!
- It's a lot of cars.
- Yes, we are going to the ramp.
Now I get a stomach ache.
Now I go under.
- Pirjo is very afraid of ramp.
Pirjo, it doesn't help you lie like that.
- Now we're in the middle.
Now brake, brake, brake.
- We are going to Åland and have fun.
My God, I hate them.
I hate these ramps.
- Goodbye Sweden!
- We will come back for a while.
We are going to Lilla Finland.
Now the captain talks to me.
Welcome Pirjo the boat.
You're fine.
- Now we have got hold of the captain.
You're not single, right?
- No.
- If you change your mind, honk.
Just honk here.
- Tuta if you become single during the journey.
So Pirjo knows about it.
- Great captain.
- Thanks.
- Thank you for your time.
- I think he looked a little so.
- No no no.
- He was craving or?
I think so.
If he was not married.
- But vase was what you said.
If he honks, then he will be single.
- Then he is single.
- You run up and get a small howling in the captain's cabin.
- Not the cab.
- No?
Where do you get your howl?
- What is sewing?
Pippa!
No, I'm not going to pip with him!
- How nice it was to dance a little.
- Yes, it was nice.
It was a real thing.
- You had a tutting, cructer.
- huh?
- You did this tutting, krruutsa.
- I can't really say no to him.
I have to say yes to everything.
- This section is in paid collaboration with Volt.
Ahaaa.
Wolt is an app where you can order home food from restaurants near you.
The best thing about volts is that it frees up a lot of time for other fun in everyday life.
Let me demonstrate.
You open the app and then just choose and wreck what to eat.
Hamburger...
And since I do not need to cook now, I get time for lots of other fun.
I can wash wash.
- Then you say you want the receipt.
- Now I forgot it.
-Yes.
-San you say ... - nice evening.
- Nice weekend.
- Then you want the receipt.
- Yes, I forgot.
Ella, the hand on the heart, are you a little disappointed with me?
- Pytte, puddle, puddle, a little.
- Did you think I'd be a little better?
- A little better.
- How old are you really?
- I'm eleven?
Hello!
- Good day!
- Hey!
- Welcome!
- Today we will be able to hang out with you at a gig in Färgelanda.
- Färgelanda is called it.
It is a small town up in Dalsland.
- We got this message yesterday and now we have to hang out with you.
We are very grateful for that.
- Yes, it was great that you wanted to do it.
- Have you ordered a rider there at ...
- Just it's careful now.
We get a choir and bread.
I think it is good.
- It's not just Red M & M's.
- Yes, so it is.
Absolutely, yes, yes.
- How long have you been doing music?
- All my life really, but I started playing piano when I was two or three years old.
- Oh!
It feels like you have absolute hearing.
- Yes it is true.
- huh?
If I sing a tone, can you say which one it is?
- I think so.
*ton*
C sharp.
F
- Mwawawaw
- It was a C major stacked, roughly.
- Mi.
- A bess.
We expect some to come.
- Yes we do.
- Hello, Hi, welcome!
- Thanks.
There was one and there was the other.
- Excuse me, does he try to plan?
Are you trying to schedule yourself?
Caught in the act.
Now he is not so cocky anymore.
- Three minutes left to Gig.
How does it feel?
-It feels good.
I am a bit nervous.
Then this humble guy-
- Sing on the small cultural association in Färgelanda.
And as he sang.
- So when I think of life that I got to live-
-and when I dream of days that I have left-
-So all the clear is my truth that will carry me-
-I know that you...
- Incredibly good job!
- Thank you, what fun to hear.
- During the break after I heard you, I ran out and contacted a music studio in Trollhättan.
And then I think we'll release a song with you when this section is released.
- Yes okay, that sounds exciting.
Yes okay, it would be fun.
- Here you have the cardan.
Go in and listen to this song today.
It is Niklas host.
- Hi, Mauri.
It is time to release my otter that I have taken care of for a year.
You are welcome to Finland.
There it is!
Finland.
And now we are here, in Finland.
And there lives Penilla and her otter.
I have never traveled so far for an otter.
- Nice.
- Nice
You emailed me and said you would release an otter.
Now we stand here and will release an otter.
How is it that?
- He was, about a year ago, very much.
He had just opened his eyes.
He was chased by a sea eagle in the middle of the open sea.
It was a Swedish family on a sailboat that saw this.
They dismissed the attack and waited for a mother to pick up her otter.
But there was never any mother.
They hoped him and called me.
He didn't even have teeth.
In the beginning I cut centimeter -sized salmon pieces that he kind of scarred in himself.
Let's see.
- There is an otter.
Check!
Hello!
You have not taught him-
You fix tables, I fix food.
See you here in a quarter.
- Now you should enjoy your last meal together in life.
- are you going to kill us?
- Yes
- Now we almost have to make a lady and the air with this fish.
- There they have their last minutes together because now it is time to head towards the lake and release this outdoor forever.
- Otis has been quite stressed during the car ride but very capable.
He has nevertheless been relatively quiet.
You are very capable darling.
You are really good.
This is my last seconds with him.
Now you should swim in the lake.
You should swim in the lake.
There, there.
- I do not know.
I've been going here for a long time.
- There is a lot to do here.
- Can you just explain what this is?
- I usually say it's a small minitivoli.
We are like a single large family living here.
- As a collective type?
- We like life.
You only live once.
- How many people live in this farm in total?
- It's type 12 people, I think.
- 12 people?
- 13 we are probably with him above the garage there is one too.
- Caravans, tractors.
- Bouncy castles.
Here it will really be the runway for Håkan's flight then.
- Does Håkan have a flight?
What is this like?
A lot.
- Bouncy castles.
- Is that a slide?
–Wa?
- Jajemans.
- What are you doing here in the yard?
- We rent out bouncy castles, limousines,-
-party buses, cars, vehicles of all kinds.
We have taxi-business, the ground contract,-
-Excavators' service, rental of residents.
We have from popcorn machines, slush machines, table chairs for big events.
Rodeo bulls, tivoli operations, tractors, cross maps.
We have snow removal, shoot some paintball.
We also have the mini golf course further down.
Then we have our 10-man bike here.
No, now it is no longer possible.
During the press, there is a Viking ship.
- Of course it does.
- Turn the wrist a little so with.
- Ouch ouch ouch
- Where are we going now?
- Now we take a little trip to Töreboda.
To the big city.
- You look with a lot of suction in my eyes at my photographer?
- Is he single?
- The photographer?
Yes.
You really look at my photographer all the time.
- Now Marica has started to pick up my photographer it feels like.
This is really a party bus.
- What should you have here?
- Here you should have a heel.
- Yes, my God, but it was nice this?
- Really.
- The same.
That was fun.
Yes, we could kind of be something.
Somewhere we leave Töreboda and continue with this section.
Thanks.
Bye.
Now only the last challenge of the week remained, which would prove to be the toughest.
But first we will end my vacation in Åland with Pirjo.
- Now we are happy!
- Yes we are fine.
- How good are you on proverbs?
- What is proverb?
No no no no!
No no no!
- Do you see these masts?
What are their names?
- The masters, yes.
- It's very popular.
It's a tourist.
Old sailboat.
- It's just what they can show here in Åland.
Now you have seen it.
Applaud!
Now we can go home.
- That is all?
- That is all.
- Now it's flat.
Oh, how cute.
- You do not.
I'll break your neck on you.
No!
No on you!
You have lost!
- I won?
- No!
But this was a great trip.
There are a lot of aunts in Sweden, but the question is if I have not found my new favorite in Pirjo.
So lively, so funny and so much yourself all the way out at your fingertips.
Now only the last challenge.
When I sat there an early Sunday morning, I was not prepared for how tricky it would be.
- I can't ... Can I even do this?
If she only knew what consequences this has for me and for this program.
- And for her.
- Hello?
- He is good at war.
- Yes.
- Yes, and now the day has come.
This is really strange.
I have a girlfriend as well.
It doesn't just feel good for any of us, I actually think.
- Fyfan what an annoying.
- It's not that often you get married without ever having met your bride in life as well.
Now she will come.
What have we done?
Hello!
Nice.
- Angelica.
- Mauri, nice.
- God, then ...
- Have you regretted it now?
- No no no!
After all, it will be a lot of paperwork if we are to divorce again.
It will be so much mecca for us.
- So we're just going to hold together?
- I thought more ...
- I understand what you meant.
- You seem great.
Angelica was there
You seem top.
You seem to be a top girl.
- You, Mauri.
- How to keep ...
- I just take in.
- And so we go.
- mm.
- Please sit down.
Before God, we have gathered for marriage between you, Mauri and Angelica.
To enter into marriage is to say yes to each other.
To the love as a gift and task.
Another gift in love and if love comes through the music.
Please turn around.
- Thanks so much Oscar for that gift.
Now we are starting to approach the great moment when you finally have to say yes to each other.
Before God and in the presence of this congregation, I ask you Elin Angelica Olander.
Do you want to take Mauri Victor Leonardo Hermundsson to your husband and love him in need and desire?
- Yes!
Before God!
And in this congregation's presence, I ask you, Mauri Victor Leonardo Hermundsson.
Want to take Elin Angelica Olander to your wife and love her in need and desire?
And what happens here is hard to explain but it was like everything got a little too much and above all I already have a girlfriend.
- Yes ...
*Angelica Harlar*
- Was it a yes?
- Wouldn't you accept everything?
What did you say?
- This was a bit surprising what happened today.
I'm a little surprised.
- But you, I'm with that.
Then we ate cake and tried to melt my betrayal jointly.
But Angelica seemed to take it easy and pleasing enough she already has a boyfriend so it seems calm.
Bengt Olof, in turn, refused the wedding cake but instead ate his onion jam.
- Jet on onion is very good.
- Is it?
- Yes absolutely.
- Oh, now you sit and eat jam.
Jet on onion is always jam.
Also on a September day.
It is exactly at the great insight about jam that we round off this program.
As we are so happy that we have done.
Then imagine what incredible experiences were hidden behind seemingly pretty boring messages.
Finnish aunts, educational children, pity troubadours, bushy otters, wonderful Western Goths and unforgettable memories.
Big thanks to Wolt!